（标志嗖嗖声）
(logo swooshes)
- 如何实例化一个 Transformers 模型。
- How to instantiate a Transformers model.
在这个视频中，我们将了解如何
In this video, we'll look at how we can create a user model
从 Transformers 库中创建一个用户模型。
from the Transformers library.
正如我们之前看到的，AutoModel 类允许
As we have seen before the AutoModel class allows
你从 Hugging Face Hub 的任何检查点
you to instantiate a pretrained model
实例化一个预训练的模型。
from any checkpoint on the Hugging Face Hub.
它将从库中挑选合适的模型类
It'll pick the right model class
来实例化适当的结构
from the library to instantiate the proper architecture
和权重负载作为里面的预训练模型。
and loads of weights as the pretrained model inside.
正如我们所看到的，当给定一个 BERT 检查点时，
As we can see, when given a BERT checkpoint
我们最终会得到一个 BertModel，同样，对于 GPT-2 或 BART 也是如此。
we end up with a BertModel and similarly, for GPT-2 or BART.
在幕后，这个 API 可以接受
Behind the scenes,this API can take the name
Hub 上一个检查点的名字
of a checkpoint on the Hub
在这种情况下，它将下载和缓存配置
in which case it will download and cache the configuration
文件以及模型权重文件。
file as well as a model weights file.
你也可以指定一个本地文件夹的路径，
You can also specify the path to a local folder
该文件夹包含一个有效的配置文件
that contains a valid configuration file and a
和一个权重模型文件。
model of weights file.
为了实例化预训练的模型，
To instantiate the pretrained model,
AutoModel API将首先打开配置
the AutoModel API will first open the configuration
文件查看应该使用的配置类。
file to look at a configuration class that should be used.
该配置类取决于模型的类型，
The configuration class depends on the type
例如 BERT、GPT-2 或 BART。
of the model BERT, GPT-2 or BART for instance.
一旦它有了一个合适的配置类，
Once it has a proper configuration class,
它就可以将该配置实例化，
it can instantiate that configuration
该配置是一个知道如何创建模型的蓝图。
which is a blueprint to know how to create the model.
它还使用这个配置类来
It also uses this configuration class to
寻找适当的模型类，然后将其
find the proper model class, which is then combined
与加载的配置相结合来加载模型。
with the loaded configuration to load the model.
这个模型还不是一个预训练过的模型，
This model is not yet a pretrained model
因为它刚刚用随机权重进行了初始化。
as it has just been initialized with random weights.
最后一步是在这个模型内加载
The last step is to load the weight from the model file
模型文件中的权重。
inside this model.
为了方便从任何检查点
To easily load the configuration of a model
或包含配置文件的文件夹中
from any checkpoint or folder containing
加载模型的配置。
the configuration file.
我们可以使用 AutoConfig 类。
We can use the AutoConfig class.
像 AutoModel 类一样，
Like the AutoModel class,
它将从库中挑选合适的配置类。
it will pick the right configuration class from the library.
我们也可以使用一个特定的类来对应
We can also use a specific class corresponding
一个检查点，但每次我们想
to a checkpoint, but we will need to change
尝试不同的模型架构时，
the code each time we want to try
我们都需要改变代码。
a different model architecture.
正如我们之前所说，一个模型的配置
As we said before, the configuration
是一个蓝图，它包含了
of a model is a blueprint that contains all the
创建模型架构所需的所有信息。
information necessary to create the model architecture.
例如，与 bert-base-cased
For instance, the BERT model associated
检查点相关的 BERT 模型有12层,
with the bert-base-cased checkpoint has 12 layers,
一个768的隐藏面和一个28996的词汇面。
a hidden side of 768 and a vocabulary side of 28,996.
一旦我们有了配置，
Once we have the configuration,
我们就可以创建一个与我们的检查点做同样架构的模型，
we can create a model that does the same architecture
但是是随机初始化的。
as our checkpoint, but is randomly initialized.
然后我们可以从头开始训练它。
We can then train it from scratch.
像任何生物 PyTorch 模块一样
Like any bio PyTorch module
我们也可以通过使用关键字参数
We can also change any part
来改变配置的任何部分。
of the configuration by using keyword arguments.
第二段代码实例化了
The second snippet of code instantiates
一个随机初始化的 BERT 模型，
a randomly initialized BERT model
有 10 层而不是 12 层。
with 10 layers instead of 12.
一旦一个模型被训练或微调，保存它是非常容易的。
Saving a model once it's trained or fine-tuned is very easy.
我们只需要使用一种安全的预训练方法。
We just have to use a safe pretrained method.
在这里，模型将被保存在当前工作目录下
Here the model will be saved in a folder named
一个名为 "my-bert-model" 的文件夹中。
"my-bert-model" inside the current working directory.
然后，这样的模型可以使用
Such a model can then be reloaded using the form
表单预训练的方法重新加载。
pretrained method.
要学习如何轻松地实现这个模型，
To learn how to easily approach this model
请查看推送的视频。
to that, check out the push to a video.